Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Committee records, 1904-1986; Series 2
  - Lower Division Committee, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1922-1924 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1924-1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1928-1933 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1933-1937 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1937-1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1928-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lower Division Committee report to Academic Council, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Misc. reports, statements, notices, forms, etc. (1) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Misc. reports, statements, notices, forms, etc. (2) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Misc. reports, statements, notices, forms, etc. (3) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Public Health Committee, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Public Health Committee, 1915-1934 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Public Health Committee, 1934-1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Public Health Committee, 1930-1960; bulk (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Publications Committee, 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Publications Committee, 1915-1926 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Publications Committee, 1927-1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Registration (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Research Committee (misc.) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Research Committee, 1920-1927 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research Committee, 1927-1938 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Research Committee, 1938-1943 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Research Committee, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Schedule Committee (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Schedule and Examination (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1894-1903 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1901-1914 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1902-1906 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1903-1907 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1906-1910 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1907-1913 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1910-1912 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1913-1914 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1916-1918 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1917-1919 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1922-1924 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1924-1925 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1925-1927 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1927-1930 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1930-1932 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1943-1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee (misc.) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Special Committee on Degrees, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Committee of Ten, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Committee of Ten (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Admissions and Financial Aid (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Admissions and Financial Aid (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee (misc.) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Studies: Subcommittee on Advising/Freshman Year (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Studies: Subcommittee on Advising/Freshman Year (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Studies: Subcommittee on Freshman Seminars (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Studies: Subcommittee on Writing (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Special Committee on University Organization, 1909-1910 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - University Policy staff meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Committee on University Policy [COUP] Agenda and minutes, 1959 Sept 24-25 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1959 Oct 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1959 Nov 5 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - COUP Budget background docs, 1959 Nov 5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1959 Dec 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - COUP Budget background docs, 1959 Dec 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Jan 7 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Feb 4 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 March 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Apr 7 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 May 5 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - COUP Minutes, 1960 May 28 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 June 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 June 17 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Sept 13 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Oct 6 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Nov 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1960 Dec 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - COUP Agenda, 1961 Jan 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 Jan 12 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 Feb 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 Mar 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 April 6 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 May 25 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1961 Oct 4 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1962 Jan 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1962 May 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1962 June 6 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1962 Dec 5 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - COUP Minutes, 1963 Jan 29 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - COUP Minutes, 1963 Apr 26 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1963 June 5 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1963 Oct 30 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - COUP Log of minutes for meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1964 May 13 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1964 June 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - COUP Miscellaneous documents, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - COUP Agenda, 1965 Jan 13 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 Jan 13 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 Mar 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 Mar 30 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 Apr 9 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - COUP Agenda, 1965 May 26 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 May 26 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - COUP Agenda, 1965 June 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 June 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - COUP Agenda, 1965 Oct 15 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - COUP Minutes, 1965 Oct 15 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1965 Dec 6 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1966 May 9 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1966 May 18 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1966 Nov 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1967 Jan 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - COUP Agenda and minutes, 1967 Nov 6 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - COUP Agenda, 1968 Mar 11 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - COUP Minutes, 1968 Mar 11 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - COUP Log of minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Restricted Material
    Access to Collection
    Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
    - Committee on Admission (1892-1895) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Admission (1896-1898) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Admissions 1906, 1925 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing (1898-1901) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1914-1916 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1917-1918 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1916-1918 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1918-1919 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1918-1920 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1919-1921 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1921-1922 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1921-1923 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1922-1923 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1924-1925 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1924-1925 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1926-1927 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1927-1929 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1929-1931 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1931-1933 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1936-1937 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1938-1940 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1945, 1946, Feb 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Admissions Committee 1956-1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing 1925-1926 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Admission and Advanced Standing 1926-1927 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing 1928-1929 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Admissions and Advanced Standing 1930-1932 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - COUP Proceedings # 1, 1959 Sep 24-25, Oct 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - COUP Proceedings # 2, 1959 Nov 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - COUP Proceedings # 3, 1960 Jan 7 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - COUP Proceedings # 4, 1960 Feb 4, Mar 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - COUP Proceedings # 5, 1960 Apr 7, May 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - COUP Proceedings # 6, 1960 June 2, June 17 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - COUP Proceedings # 7, 1960 Sep-Dec (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - COUP Proceedings # 8, 1961 Jan-Mar (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - COUP Proceedings # 9, 1961 Apr 6, May 25 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - COUP Proceedings # 10, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - COUP Proceedings # 11, 1962 May 2, June 6 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - COUP Proceedings # 12, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - COUP Proceedings # 13, 1963 Oct 30 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - COUP Proceedings # 14, 1964 May 13, June 3 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - COUP Proceedings # 15, 1965 Jan-June (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - COUP. Academic Space Administration memo, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - COUP. Correspondence and memos, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - COUP. Correspondence and memos, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - COUP. Correspondence and memos, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - COUP. Correspondence and memos, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - COUP. Correspondence and memos, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - COUP. Draft report on SU executive administration, circa 1955 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - COUP. Grading system, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - COUP. Graduate student housing, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - COUP. Membership lists and appointments, 1959-1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - COUP. Miscellaneous statements (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - COUP. Notices of meetings, 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - COUP. Pending items (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - COUP. Problems of student drinking, circa 1962 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - COUP. Report regarding honors programs, circa 1960 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - COUP. Function "O" financial sheets, 1967 Oct 31 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - COUP. Sponsored research financial sheets, 1967 Oct 31 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - COUP. Staff benefits financial sheets, 1967 Oct 31 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Research, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Committee on Research, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
  - Committee on Research, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Research, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Research, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
  - Committee on Research, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Research, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1-9)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 10-19)
- Academic Council records, 1911-1969; Accession ARCH_1980_026
  - Academic Council, actions and correspondence, 1911-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council, actions and correspondence, 1921-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council, actions and correspondence, 1929-1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council, actions and correspondence, 1937-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1911-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1942-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes and correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Division, Committee on, 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Judicial Procedures, Committee on, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - President's Student Advisory Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Public Exercises, 1953-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Public Exercises, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Public Exercises, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Public Exercises, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Public Exercises, Century 21, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Public Exercises, Freshman Convocation, 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Public Exercises, Subcommittee on Film, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Public Health, Committee on, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Registrar, 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Registrar's Advisory Committee, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Student Faculty Entertainment Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Student Financial Aid, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Student Publications, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1957-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Undergrad admissions, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Undergrad admissions, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate Education, Committee on, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Education, Committee on, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - University Libraries, Committee on, [1968-1969] (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - University Publications, Committee on, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Academic Council records, 1960-1982; Accession ARCH_1982_013
  - COUP, September 1960-March 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Community Self-discipline, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - StC Subcommittee on Academic Freedom (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - COUP, September 1959-January 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - COUP, June 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - COUP, April 1961-April 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - COUP, May 1962-April 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - COUP Re Academic Pressure, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - COUP, February 1960-April 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - COUP, May 1960-August 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Staff Compensation, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Student Health Center (Task Force to Study), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Committee on ROTC, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Residential Education, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - University Committee on Religious Activities, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Japan Fund (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Panel on Internal Affirmative Action (P-IAA) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Human Relations Commission, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Human Relations Commission, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Institution, Advisory Panel to President (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Golf Course Advisory Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financial Awards (External) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Interim Panel for Faculty Hearing Groups (P-FHG), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Educational Inquiry (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate binders containing minutes and supportive documents from Senate meetings and committees, 1979-1982 (Box 4-12)
- Memorial resolutions, Accession ARCH_1985_015
  - Ackerman, Robert W. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Ephraim D. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Addis, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alden, Raymond M. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aldrich, Putnam C. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alexander, Wallace M. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allardice, Robert E. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Warren D. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Almack, John C. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alvarez-Tostado, Claudio (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Angell, Frank (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arnautoff, Victor (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arnold, John Edward (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baran, Paul Alexander (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barnett, George De Forest (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barr, Margaret Catherine (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bartky, Adolph John (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bassett, Lee Emerson (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Baumberger, James Percy (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Beach, Walter Greenwood (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beard, Paul Jay (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beasley, Shadworth O. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Begle, Edward Griffith (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bennett, Merrill Kelley (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bennion, Edward Graham (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bergman, Stefan (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bergstrom, Francis William (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bingham, Joseph Walter (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Birnie, Hans Frederick (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Blackwelder, Eliot (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Blaisdell, Frank Ellsworth, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Blattner, Helene (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Blauth, Henry (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Blichfeldt, Hans Frederik (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bloch, Felix (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bloomfield, Arthur L. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Boezinger, Bruno (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bolin, Rolf Ling (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brand, Carl Fremont (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Brandt, Karl (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Branner, John Casper (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Brenner, James Emmett (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Briggs, William Dinsmore (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Brodrick, Richard Godfrey (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Brown, Harold Chapman (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Brown, Joseph Grant (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Brown, Walter Henry (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bugge, Elwyn B. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Burlingame, Leonas Lancelot (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bush, Chilton Rowlette (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Campbell, Douglas Houghton (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Canning, John Bennet (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Cannon, Henry Lewin (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Carlsmith, J. Merrill (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Carroll, Joseph Snyder (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Carruth, William Herbert (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Carter, Earl Kendall (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Castaneda, Alfredo (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Cathcart, Arthur Martin (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Chandler, Loren R. (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Chapin, Leland Taylor (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Churchill, Henry Lloyd (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Clark, Arthur Bridgman (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Clark, George Archibald (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Clark, George Thomas (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Clebsch, William Anthony (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Clifton, Charles Egolf (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Coester, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Conroy, Esther (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Cooper, William Alpha (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Cootner, Paul Harold (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Coover, John Edgar (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Cottrell, Edwin Angell (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Cowan, John Francis (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Cowdery, Karl Montague (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Cowley, William Harold (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Craig, Hardin (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Crawford, Albert Cornelius (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Crook, Welton J. (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Cross, Charles Norman (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Cubberley, Ellwood Patterson (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Cuddeback, Murray (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Culver, George Bliss (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Danforth, Charles Haskell (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Davis, Joseph Stancliffe (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Davis, William Hawley (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Deering, Frank Prentiss (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - deLeew, Karel (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Depres, Emile (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Dickey, Lloyd Blackwell (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Dickson, Ernest Charles (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Doane, Rennie Wilbur (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Dowrie, George William (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Doyle, Edwin Joseph (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Drew, Elmer Reginald (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Duncan, William Bryan (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Dunn, Theodore Saunders (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Durand, William Frederick (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Faber, Harold Kniest (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Fagan, Elmer Daniel (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Fairclough, Henry Rushton (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Farmer, Edward McNeil (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Farnsworth, Helen Cherington (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Farnsworth, Paul Randolph (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Faulkner, Ray N. (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Faville, David Ernest (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Ferris, Gordon Floyd (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Ferris, Roxana S. (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Finch, Volney Cecil (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Fish, John C. L. (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Fisher, Harold Henry (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Fisher, Walter Kenrick (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Flugge-Lotz, Irmgard (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Forsythe, George Elmer (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Foster, Benjamin Oliver (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Frankel, Hermann Ferdinand (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Franklin, Edward Curtis (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Gardner, David Charles (Box 1, Folder 120)